Marvel Studios Assembled: The Making of She-Hulk: Attorney at
Law is a documentary film directed by Brad Baruh.
Join the likes of Tatiana Maslany, Mark Ruffalo, Tim Roth, and Benedict Wong as they
reveal how Marvel Studios’ She-Hulk: Attorney at Law was conceived and shaped.
Discover what it took for She-Hulk’s creators to pull off the show’s tricky tone and deliver Marvel Studios’ first
truly comedic series – one that boldly breaks the fourth wall to acknowledge its own audience, no less!
Self, played by Tatiana Maslany.
Self, played by Mark Ruffalo.
Self, played by Tim Roth.
Self, played by Benedict Wong.
Self, played by Ginger Gonzaga.
Self, played by Josh Segarra.
Marvel Studios: Assembled is an American anthology television docuseries
of specials created for the streaming service Disney+.
Produced by Marvel Studios, each special goes behind-the-scenes of a Marvel Studios Disney+ series or film, particularly those
within the Marvel Cinematic Universe (MCU), with the creatives, exploring the process of creating each series or film.
The series was first announced in February 2021.
Marvel Studios: Assembled premiered on March 12, 2021, with subsequent specials releasing
shortly after a Disney+ series' completion or a film's Disney+ release.
14 specials were released for Phase Four of the MCU, followed by 9 specials released for Phase Five projects through
2024, including one for the first season of the Marvel Studios Animation series X-Men '97 (2024).
The special for Agatha All Along (2024) was released for free
on Marvel Entertainment's YouTube channel.
Assembled received positive responses for showcasing how each series or film came
together, particularly with the technical aspects and franchise connectivity.
The film explores themes of superhero, behind the scenes,
making of, marvel cinematic universe (mcu).